top-clocks.com 2016-11-07

# Privacy Policy - WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **admin@WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM**.

At WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM and how it is used.

### Log Files

Like many other Web sites, WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

 **WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM** does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on **WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM**.

.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to **WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM** and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

### Our Advertising Partners

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM** privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

 ** _Our advertising partners include:_**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on **WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM** send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

 **WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM** has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM** 's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

### Affiliate Disclaimer

 **WWW.TOP-CLOCKS.COM** is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.

The price shown may have changed since the time we last updated them. The actual price of the product on the Amazon site at the time of purchase will govern the sale.

Amazon and Amazon.com are trademarks, registered trademarks or trade dress of Amazon in the U.S. and/or other countries

### Email

Our service sends no email notifications, though we provide an easy way to subscribe to the RSS email delivery via third-party service. When you enter your email address and click "Follow this Feed via Email", you'll be sent to the website blogtrottr.com and with an opportunity to track changes in price via Email. You should consult the respective privacy policy of this third-party service.

### Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
